Contact

alexmcmillan1013@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/alex-mcmillan-bsn-rn-0269489b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Patient Experience
Service Excellence
Transformational Leadership

Alex McMillan BSN, RN

Nurse Manager at HCA Houston Healthcare Clear Lake Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Bachelors prepared RN with 6+ years experience. Currently serving as the Nurse Manager for 4 units specialized in Comprehensive Stroke, Ortho Trauma, Neurosurgery, Bariatrics, and Colorectal Post Op Care.

My passion is leadership in Nursing. I believe it is our duty as experienced nurses to grow our new nurses in their role and to be a role model to them! It is an honor and privilege to serve in the healthcare field.

Experience

HCA Gulf Coast Division

7 years 5 months

Nurse Manager of General Surgery & Surgical Intermediate January 2013 - Present (7 years 5 months)

Webster, Texas

Nurse Manager

Assistant Nurse Manager Stroke Unit June 2014 - August 2016 (2 years 3 months)

Webster, Texas

Recipient of DAISY Award 2016

Registered Nurse

January 2013 - June 2014 (1 year 6 months)

Webster, Texas

Floor Nurse on Rehab, and Surgical Intermediate. Served also as Preceptor and Relief Charge Nurse during this time.

Education

The University of Texas at Arlington

Bachelor's of Science Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2015 - 2016)

ECPI University

Associate's degree in Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse \cdot (2011 - 2012)